let questions = [
  {
    num: 1,
    question: "What does HTML stands for?",
    answer: "C.Hyper Text Markup Language",
    option: [
      "A.Hyper Type Multi Language",
      "B.Hyper Text Multiple Language",
      "C.Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "D. Home Text Multi Language"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 2,
    question: "What does CSS stands for?",
    answer: "A.Cascading Style Sheet",
    option: [
      "A.Cascading Style Sheet",
      "B.Cute Style Sheet ",
      "C.Computer Style Sheet",
      "D.Compressed Style Sheet"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 3,
    question: "What does PHP stands for?",
    answer: "B.Hypertext PreProcessor",
    option: [
      "A.Home text preprocessor",
      "B.Hypertext PreProcessor",
      "C.Hypertext PreProgramming",
      "D.Pre Hypertext Processor"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 4,
    question: "What does SQL stands for?",
    answer: "D.Structural Query Language",
    option: [
      "A.Stylesheet Query Language",
      "B.Strength Query Language",
      "C.Simple Query Language",
      "D.Structural Query Language"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 5,
    question: "What does XML stands for?",
    answer: "A.Extensible Markup Language",
    option: [
      "A.Extensible Markup Language",
      "B.External Markup Language",
      "C.Extented Multi Language",
      "D.Extra Markup Language"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 6,
    question: "What Express js is?",
    answer: "C.A npm module / library",
    option: [
      "A.A framework",
      "B.Extended javascript",
      "C.A npm module / library",
      "D.A query language"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 7,
    question: "What does JsON stands for?",
    answer: "A.Javascript Object Notation",
    option: [
      "A.Javascript Object Notation",
      "B.Javascript and Node",
      "C.Java object Notation",
      "D.Java and node"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 8,
    question: "What does SDLC stands for?",
    answer: "B.Software Development Life Cycle",
    option: [
      "A.Software Development Licence",
      "B.Software Development Life Cycle",
      "C.Soft Document Licence",
      "D.Software Decoding Life cycle"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 9,
    question: "What does .jsx in react stands for?",
    answer: "D.Javascript and XML",
    option: [
      "A.Javascript and ML",
      "B.Extended Javascript",
      "C.Javascript extension",
      "D.Javascript and XML"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 10,
    question: "What is Object?",
    answer: "B.Instance of Class",
    option: [
      "A.Collection of items",
      "B.Instance of Class",
      "C.Instance of Method",
      "D.Instance of Array"
    ]
  }

];
